This program is brought to you by Stanford University.
Please visit us at stanford.edu
Thank You. I am honored to be with you today at your commencement
from one of the finest universities in the world.
Truth be told I never graduated from college
and this is the closest I've ever gotten to a college graduation.
Today I want to tell you three stories from my life. That's it.
No big deal. Just three stories.
The first story is about connecting the dots.
I dropped out of Reed College after the first 6 months,
but then stayed around as a drop-in
for another 18 months or so before I really quit.
So why did I drop out?
It started before I was born.
My biological mother was a young, unwed graduate student,
and she decided to put me up for adoption.
She felt very strongly that I should be adopted by college graduates,
so everything was all set for me to
be adopted at birth by a lawyer and his wife.
Except that when I popped out they decided
at the last minute that they really wanted a girl.
So my parents, who were on a waiting list,
got a call in the middle of the night asking: "We have an unexpected
baby boy; do you want him?"
They said: "Of course." My biological mother later found out that
my mother had never graduated from college
and that my father had never graduated from high school.
She refused to sign the final adoption papers.